C23 NAVINT is a doctrine-driven AI decision-superiority augmentation
for Maven Smart System NATO and Allied C2 platforms.
A single self-contained HTML file that runs offline on a 16 GB
tactical workstation, with no installation, no server, no proprietary stack.
Every workflow is bound to an Allied Joint Publication,
with a citable provenance.
The default mission embeds the Eastern Flank illustrative scenario
from the challenge statement.
NATO eFP battle groups in EE/LV/LT/PL.
SNMG1 in the Baltic. OPFOR forces from LMD, Kaliningrad and Belarus.
Critical Undersea Infrastructure nodes (Estlink 2, Baltic Connector).
Two suspect dark-AIS vessels (DARK ECHO 1 and 2) render in red.
The COP fuses commercial AIS, OSINT, RADAR, ELINT and FUSION events
into a single layer-toggleable view.
The Force Tally shows units by side and by domain,
including CYBER as the fifth operational domain per AJP-3.20.
Top-bar tiles surface FPCON, CBRN, PNT and CIS PACE in real time.
The Joint Targeting Cycle is fully materialised per AJP-3.9.
Six-phase JTC indicator on the top bar.
The JPTL with HVT, HPT and TST categories,
the F2T2EA stage, CDE rating and per-target restrictions.
Restricted Target List and No-Strike List as separate lists.
Every engagement decision gates through these inputs.
Every CoA that would engage a Time-Sensitive Target opens a
Rules-of-Engagement authorisation modal.
The modal surfaces matching TSTs with their CDE rating,
the full RTL, the NSL, and an explicit Authorise-or-Deny decision.
Operational wargaming runs in-platform without any external simulator.
Every NATO CoA is matched pairwise against every OPFOR CoA
through a deterministic seeded outcome model.
Colour-coded matrix; best-and-worst summary per friendly option.
The cascade-effects engine is doctrine-as-code.
Each rule cites its source Allied Joint Publication.
AJP-3.1 for naval interdiction. AJP-4.4 for movement.
AJP-3.20 for cyber.
Every analytical output is auditable back to the doctrinal text.
Personnel Recovery per AJP-3.7 implements the five-task sequence:
Reported, Located, Supported, Recovered, Reintegrated.
Movement per AJP-3.13 / 4.4 manages MSR / ASR / APOD / SPOD,
status-coloured. Naval interdiction polygon editable on the COP.
Third-party integration is a first-order design constraint.
Three documented JSON schemas plus the AIS schema.
Wrapped in a CycloneDX 1.7 / ECMA-424 envelope covering software,
services, crypto, hardware, ML, ops and operational data.
Live-feed adapter, OPORD generator, and the foundation-model seam.
The platform ships as a strictly air-gapped runtime.
Dependencies mirrored under dist/airgap/vendor.
A CycloneDX attestation accompanies the bundle, ready for signing.
Spec coverage 98.6 %. C23 NAVINT, by CONFIANZA23. Ready for evaluation.